cooljapannow.jp 2019-11-25

# CDJapan : Privacy Policy (Personal Information Protection Policy)

Privacy Policy (Personal Information Protection Policy) Neowing corporation (hereinafter referred to as "the Company"), hereby declares that, in order for customers to use the services of the Company, such as mail order sales and the provision of digital content via the internet, with peace of mind, the Company is aware of the importance of personal information, shall adhere to laws and regulations on the protection of personal information, has prescribed the policy set forth below, has established a personal information protection management system for the realization of this policy, and shall implement, maintain, and improve this.

The Company shall clearly prescribe the purpose of use when acquiring personal information that will be used in its business, shall indicate this purpose, and shall only obtain that of content within the range required for the achievement of the purpose of use. In addition, after personal information has been obtained, it shall not be used for any purpose other than that presented at the time of acquisition. The Company shall conduct thorough education on its employees, etc. in order to ensure that personal information is not used outside of its purpose of use.

The Company, in regard to the personal information provided for use in the business of the Company, shall adhere to laws, regulations, governmental policies, and other rules on the handling of personal information. Furthermore, the Company has established a personal information management system that conforms with Japanese Industrial Standard "Personal information protection management systems - Requirements" (JIS Q15001), and protects personal information.

The Company shall sufficiently analyze and maintain awareness of the risks relating to the personal information handled by the Company, and shall take measures to prevent and rectify the leakage, loss, or damage of personal information.

In the event of receiving a complaint or inquiry regarding the handling of personal information, the Company shall promptly investigate the relevant facts, etc. relating to this, and shall respond in good faith within a reasonable period.

The Company shall keep in mind trends in network technology, public opinion regarding the protection of personal information, as well as the content of opinions and complaints, etc. received from its customers, and shall continually improve the personal information protection management system.

Established March 23, 2006  
Amended May 25, 2018  
Neowing corporation  
Representative Director Fumio Katagiri

### Inquiries

Personal Information Complaint and Inquiry Help Desk, Neowing corporation  
3F, JL Nihonbashi Building, 1-10-15, Nihonbashi Horidome-cho, Chuo-ku,  
Tokyo 103-0012  
e-mail: info-pro@neowing.co.jp  
Telephone: 03-3665-4947 (Business hours: Weekdays 10:00–18:00)

## Handling of Personal Information

  1. Business Operator Handling Personal Information  
Neowing Corporation.
  2. Personal Information Protection Manager  
Group Leader, Business Supervisory Group
  3. Purposes of Use of Personal Information  

    1. Member management
    2. Acceptance of orders
    3. Packing and shipping of products, etc.
    4. Collection of bill through credit card payments or cash on delivery, etc.
    5. Transmission of email magazine
    6. Transmission of notification emails concerning promotions and information on new products, etc.
    7. Response to various inquiries and after sales service
    8. Notifications on matters required for the operation of the website
    9. Provision of a points service, etc.
    10. Packing and shipping of products, etc. by gift delivery requests
In addition, the Company, for the improvement of its services, may use personal information by collecting and referencing it as statistical information in a form by which an individual cannot be identified or specified.
  4. Contracting of the Handling of Personal Information  
The Company, when providing shipping and bill collection, etc. services, may entrust all or a part of the handling of the personal information provided by the customer to a credit card company, payment systems provider, or delivery company, etc. When entrusting the handling of personal information, the Company shall select companies that protect personal information to a sufficient standard, and shall take the appropriate measures, such as through the execution of a contract.
  5. Handling of Credit Card Information  
The Company shall handle the credit card information provided by the customer in accordance with the following.  

    1. Purpose of use: Payment for purchased products
    2. Name of party obtaining information: Neowing corporation
    3. Recipients of information: Various payment providers and payment agents
    4. Storage period: Payment agent GMO Payment Gateway, Inc.’s "PG Multipayment Service" is used for credit card payment and registration. None of the credit card information of customers is stored at the Company.
  6. Personal Information Security  
Registered information of the customer, for the protection of privacy and security, is password protected. In addition, this website uses software called SSL (Secure Socket Layer) for security when customer information is transmitted. The use of SSL allows transmission of the customer’s personal information and credit card details, etc. from the customer’s PC to the server in encrypted form, and prevents the theft or tampering, etc. of information, thereby allowing for personal information to be transmitted securely via the internet.
  7. Cookies  
The website uses a technology called cookies. Cookies are a mechanism for temporarily storing specific information required for communications on the personal computer used by the customer as data, and identifying the customer based on this data each time that the customer connects to the website. The Company uses cookies for shopping cart and login management. Therefore, if a customer does not permit the use of cookies, a part of the Company’s services may become unavailable. Whether or not to allow use of cookies can be set on the customer’s browser. We ask that customers check their settings as necessary.
  8. Procedures for the Disclosure, etc. of Personal Information  
The Company is aware that customers have the right to request the disclosure, notification on purpose of use, amendment, addition, deletion, suspension of use, and suspension of provision to third parties, etc. of personal information (hereinafter referred to as "Disclosure, etc."), and if it receives such a request from a customer, shall promptly respond to this without objection. Customers are asked to direct inquiries on the specific procedures for this to the help desk stated below. It should be noted that the fee specified by the Company may be charged for requests for the disclosure of personal information and notification of the purpose of use of personal information; the Company asks for the understanding of its customers.
  9. Collection of Information from Minors  
The Company shall not consciously collect personal information from minors under the age of thirteen. In the event of a minor under the age of thirteen providing personal information to the Company without the consent of their parent or guardian, the parent or guardian of the child may make a request to the Company by email for the deletion of information of said minor from the Company’s database, and for the stopping of the provision of information on services to the minor.  
Please contact the help desk stated below for inquiries concerning this.

Personal Information Complaint and Inquiry Help Desk, Neowing corporation  
3F, JL Nihonbashi Building, 1-10-15, Nihonbashi Horidome-cho, Chuo-ku, Tokyo 103-0012  
e-mail: info-pro@neowing.co.jp  
Telephone: 03-3665-4947 (Business hours: Weekdays 10:00–18:00)

Member information can be checked and changed, etc. from the URL below instead of making a request as described above: 

### [Click here to check or change, etc. member information (with link)](https://www.cdjapan.co.jp/z/my/)

  10. Inquiries and complaints regarding the handling of personal information  
Customers are asked to direct any opinions, complaints, questions, or inquiries regarding the handling of personal information by the Company to its Personal Information Complaint and Inquiry Help Desk stated above.

The Accredited Personal Information Protection Organization Joined by the Company

The Company is a member of the Japan Institute for Promotion of Digital Economy and Community, which has been certified as an accredited personal information protection organization based on Article 37 of the Act on the Protection of Personal Information. Customers are asked to address complaints regarding the handling of personal information by the Company to this institute.

Japan Institute for Promotion of Digital Economy and Community  
Personal Information Protection Complaint and Inquiry Office  
Address: 12F, Roppongi First Building, 1-9-9, Roppongi, Minato-ku, Tokyo 106-0032  
Telephone: 03-5860-7565  
Toll-free telephone number: 0120-700-779

## Protection of Personal Information of Customers in an EEA Member Country

Customers residing within an EEA member country, which comprises of European Union (EU) member countries, Iceland, Liechtenstein, and Norway, are asked to bear the following additional terms in mind:

Customers' personal information is forwarded to a server in Japan, where it is stored. Japan conforms to the standards for data protection sent by the European Commission, and all personal data received by the Company is accordingly handled.

The Customer may make a request to the Company to access their personal data, correct inaccurate personal data, and delete personal data. Contact info@cdjapan.co.jp for further information. Furthermore, in the event of being unsatisfied by the Company’s handling of personal information, a customer may file a complaint with a regulatory authority of an EEA member country.
